[Music]
Please show
me one result they bill credit last
class
they used it you managed you became d
regret of you c b right so they bill be
looking inside class of band it bill get dem
today right so d pack branded sir
using d shymfting band again you bounce likely
different quantity but
never d list of interest
quality
probability series
one form of writing
[praise]
expected x
d probability of d union of
multiple events right this led and equal
you d sum of d probability
they can write this result ok
probability of d joint event by the
sum of the probability of individual
events ok this r d results they bill
just cup using dem you
sum of d profuse today
ok so
they talk about multiple solution
concepts but bande talk right so d
first one character assembly correctness d
second don't be talk about like date
talk you me led which they already look at  One
example of regret optical ucb and
ucb1 more correctly and d popular one people se
ucb d refer you ucb1 right and give
what it d third one et
right n which is probably approximately
correct
bound with some probability right a date
your close n you di you solution
date you want you give right so what bill look at
today and
pack bonus
start off d very very simple dem that
you have to use this just you get you
start it a so I have an input which is
I bill give you an
delta and what time
return you bill be absolute on close you
d optical on with probability 1 -
delta
very high probability of finisher running
with d very high probability I bill give
you n yes which is appcil on close you
d true of d pay remember the
pack guarantee was full rot right so
most pack d pack style algorithm
essential take place
on this apps
so I am writing
an paper date way bill  give you you read so dat
cc but you you forgive it unfortunately I
bill style you the online translation of
notation so dat aa you can compare n cross
multiply ok
and this paper is way way way butter return di
you c b p
so reflexively you can understand d
paper when you read it n this is n
d median elimination by or 11 der shahi
manor and shei mansoor ok it's like action
elimination per reinforcement planning ok so
d nice think about this ok I bill tel you
nice things about d paper later but d
really nice think about d paper so I can easily very simply just k c five if
I get a good enough
estimate per h am right IF you get a
good enough estimate of d reward ka wish give I can say dat
with d very high
probability I bill be
right so it's always a small chase tha I
bill co round
saying her so d idea is very  So simple, so I
take an ordinary bill and pull it into a multiple
times
good estimate of d
of expectation right, d probability with which
you're going to come up with one and what ever right,
so whatever is the expectation
parameter and just cup pulling multiple
times multiple bills get a good estimate
of d expectation I bill do per h of d
arms tha I have
right and once I have a good expectation which I have so
two is no co on play the arms tha
highest
what time
date is actually number okay remember I take
epsilon and everything put jivan jo of this is
actually it's actually number right so tha
magic number ho did I produce jo
of this things so date you know date
you're going to produce that time you produce
magic number so it's very simple so let's
make things a little formal
so we call this algorithm
no
input absolut delta is n  Applause Delta
Pack
what is absolute on Delta Pack
defined it in the earlier lecture right its
note Delta Pack gives you date whatsoever
guarantee is you are talking about right it is
on Delta Pack common sample complexity number
of times you pull d arms in life
order ka handbag squad in people
and by Delta
well so this part
so half hai that today well what is other
and say well today
and by mistake right please pointed out to me so I
bill correct it you care
with you
proof it well d sample complex you
parts they don't have you proof date they just have you
proof date
so for back let
a prime
PNR
spotting you d best of they no date right
so date it is at list stepsil on aave
from k star restart
d k star of a prime is at list
capsule on aave from k star rest so
date mens it's
an bed on
right so common chadar more de rapsil on
close you d true I don't care defense
collect dem happy because me guarantee is
Satish I  really have you really about making a mistake which
in this how is it selecting
an ordinary date give it more than the actual from the true
award true optimal okay so basically
they are looking at d event so
this is what they want looking at right so this is
d how
prime minister
correct
it is k a prime is greater give k a
star than my output
test are on me you select a prime as d
best term at list this condition has you been
satisfied
per sir this condition this happen can see the same they need this
condition right so if
you be reported as d best but
give a star so
this condition also already were this is not
really d probability was yes
prime bill b d best
only looking at some sub b weight of date okay it's not jo
d and but this bill give me a
list has
mount on d probability so date is
essential same you are looking at this event okay so
what is  Happening her
late se date is me
list this
making
[praise]
start
automatically mens tha idhar k a prime hj tu
b more den absol on right more den
tu about and
why this star sold b absol
star
plus
so you can think of cases where this is actually her right k
star rational recommend k of a star hj
tu b and below right it bill b more den
sil on a way forget about appcil on way
you
right per cases very estimating
star give this bill also have you be here
its again it bill b more den it's
alone ave so interesting how is this when it is in
between
friend and just checking they independence
events and something about
on d total probability is right some
making simple and simple per me and know what happens her
you kid of in d son of space right so can i play around here
so what bill b d how her i
power
-2 apps
plus apps
what they need so two no is adjust this one so the
solid things
basically what they are looking at
right and you will be left key I want this
probability delta
this is d problem
by mistake
what is this which me apps everything k and k
mines one so they bill take little tower k so this
whole thing should be simplified you
delta by k let so that's what I
sold be looking
magic number real
necessary error
further probability
selecting actions you can which derive the
required basically turns out
date it turns out date
it's almost impossible to get read
of this one by epsilon
squared turn right I want you I remember what I said
about d pack and analysis so I
bill give you an absol on delta and no the
interesting part test telling me how you can I
change its epsilon on delta with these
fuel samples  possible
correct so in this how and telling you date
this is d sample complexity right and k
figure scene you place right it turn
people of this k
depend on poet
at list one's right I have you try every
atlist one so I can get off d k also right only
playing I can try and
minimize this
well I can try
right and tree you get it up you people k
dependency right and they have k web launch I can try you
move in date direction and
one side rich there I will probably be in
left with trying you get read of this you every
right and tree you make d true * 3 / 2 and
1.7 and something really sorry you know ho you
things
but more which list this one by apps on
square and people delta something dat bill have
you leave it okay
[music]
[applause]